https://www.retrohifi.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - Retro Refurb
Skip to content
Retro Refurb
Thinking of doing up your home?
Terms of Use & Privacy Policy
We ask that you take the time to carefully read our website Terms of Use & Privacy Policy before you continue to browse the content.
This website does not collect or retain any personally identifying information.
We may update these from time to time & reserve the right to alter our Privacy Policy & Site Terms  without advance notice.
You can view our policies by following the links below to open them in PDF format.
PPRIVACY POLICY – General
TERMS & CONDITIONS
Thank You.
Replacement UPVC Windows for Your Home
Double Glazed Windows and Doors Energy Efficiency (US)
Composite Doors for the Entrance and for the Back of Your Property
Lowering your Utility Costs With Double Glazing
Home Extensions and Conservatories
Rustic Exterior Stable Doors For Your Home
COOKIES & PRIVACY COOKIES ON THIS WEBSITE
We use cookies to improve your browsing experience. Parts of the website may not work as expected without them. By continuing to browse this site, closing or ignoring this message, you are consenting to our use of cookies.
RECENT POSTS
Trickle Vents Used for Ventilating Double Glazed Windows
Conservatory Styles and Designs as Home Extensions
Replacement UPVC Windows for Your Home
Double Glazed Windows and Doors Energy Efficiency (US)
Composite Doors for the Entrance and for the Back of Your Property
SITE SEARCH
Copyright © 2020 Retro Refurb. Powered by WordPress. Theme: Spacious by ThemeGrill.
Home
Privacy Policy
Contact
